https://www.velan.com/en/privacy/

Products
ProductsCryogenic valvesCast steel Cryogenic valvesCryogenic gate valvesCryogenic globe valvesCryogenic swing check valvesAPI 602 small forged cryogenic valvesCryogenic gate valvesCryogenic globe valvesCryogenic check valvesTorqseal cryogenic triple-offset valvesCryogenic triple-offset valvesMemoryseal ball valvesCryogenic split-body ball valvesCryogenic top-entry ball valvesCryogenic control valvesQuench relief valvesBellows seal control valvesCryogenic control valvesDMS magnetic safety deviceGate, globe, and check valvesPressure seal (forged and cast steel) valvesPressure seal flexible wedge gate valvesPressure seal parallel slide gate valvesPressure seal globe valvesPressure seal y-pattern globe valvesPressure seal swing check valvesPressure seal tilting disc check valvesPressure seal piston check valvesPressure seal y-pattern piston check valvesBolted bonnet high pressure valves (large forged) valvesBolted bonnet flexible wedge gate valvesBolted bonnet parallel slide gate valvesBolted bonnet globe valvesBolted cover swing check valvesBolted cover piston check valvesBolted bonnet bellows seal flexible wedge gate valvesBolted bonnet bellows seal globe valvesCast steel (bolted bonnet) valvesGate valves (API 600)Globe valvesSwing check valvesCryogenic gate valvesCryogenic globe valvesCryogenic check valvesCryogenic swing check valvesCast steel bellows seal gateCast steel bellows seal globeCast HF Acid gate valvesCast HF Acid globe valvesCast HF Acid swing check valvesCast stainless steel corrosion resistant valvesFlanged gate valves (API 603)Flanged globe valvesFlanged swing check valvesSocket weld/threaded gate valvesSocket weld/threaded globe valvesSocket weld/threaded check valvesAPI 602 small forged valvesGate valvesGlobe valvesCheck valvesPiston check valvesExtended body gate valvesInclined globe valvesContinuous blowdown valvesBoiler plant service valvesCryogenic gate valvesCryogenic globe valvesBellows seal gate valvesExtended body bellows seal gate valvesBellows seal globe valvesAPI 602 HF acid small forged gate valvesAPI 602 small forged HF acid globe valvesSmall forged HF acid check valvesBonnetless valvesBonnetless globe valvesBellows seal globe valves, hermetically-sealed y-patternPiston check valvesXB series bonnetless globe valves (discontinued)Dual-plate check valves (Proquip)Wafer type - PW dual-plate check valvesSolid Lug type - PL, PM, dual plate check valvesDouble flanged type - PF, PG dual plate check valveHub end type - PH dual plate check valveButt weld end type - PZ dual plate check valveKnife gate valvesBolted bonnet metal-seated knife gate valvesBolted bonnet resilient-seated knife gate valvesStandard metal-seated knife gate valvesStandard resilient-seated knife gate valvesRAMA easy maintenance valves for nuclear serviceRAMA globe valvesRAMA BELLOWS SEAL globe valvesCLAMA check valvesRAMA LIGHT intrumentation valvesHF Acid valvesCast HF acid valvesCast HF Acid gate valvesCast HF Acid globe valvesCast HF Acid swing check valvesAPI 602 small forged HF acid valvesAPI 602 HF acid small forged gate valvesAPI 602 small forged HF acid globe valvesSmall forged HF acid check valvesQuarter-turn valvesMemoryseal ball valvesSplit-body ball valvesUnibody ball valvesTop-entry ball valvesEP-2000 end-entry ball valvesEE-1000 end-entry ball valvesHB-2000 one-piece ball valvesCryogenic split-body ball valvesCryogenic top-entry ball valvesSecuraseal metal-seated ball valvesCast split-body flanged ball valvesTop-entry in-line repairable ball valvesType L high-temperature metal-seated ball valvesType N severe service forged metal-seated ball valvesR-series cast and forged metal-seated ball valvesHP series forged ball valvesHP series forged ball valvesPower Ball valvesPower Ball valvePower ComboVTP-2000 high performance three-piece ball valvesVTP-2000 3-piece ball valvesValvac general purpose ball valvesVOP-1000 one-piece ball valvesVEE-2000 end-entry ball valvesV3P-1000 three-piece ball valvesTorqseal® triple offset valvesCryogenic triple-offset valvesTriple offset valves 2.0Velflex high performance cryogenic butterfly valvesButt weld end valvesFlanged valvesCoker ball valvesFour-way switch valvesIsolation valvesRing valveHigh pressure valve (hydrodrill valve)Cap-Tight batch digester capping valvesCapping valvesSteam trapsBimetallic steam trapsType MFA & MFAS compressed air drain trapsType MFT & MFTS float bimetallic steam trapsType N forged HP/HT steam trapsType Q250 hermetically-sealed steam trapsType SPF & SP high capacity piston-operated steam trapsType SSF steam trapsType TS, TSF & SF forged steam trapsPiping King package unitsThermodynamic steam trapsType HPTD & VTS thermodynamic steam trapsBellows seal valvesBellows seal bolted bonnet high pressure valves (large forged)Bolted bonnet bellows seal flexible wedge gate valvesBolted bonnet bellows seal globe valvesBellows seal cast steel valves (Bolted Bonnet)Cast steel bellows seal gateCast steel bellows seal globeBellows seal API 602 small forged valvesExtended body bellows seal gate valvesBellows seal globe valvesBellows seal gate valvesVelan ABV ValvesIndustries servedNuclear powerPowerOil & gasRefiningChemicalPulp & paperMarineMiningLNG & cryogenicsWater & wastewaterServiceResearch and DevelopmentMaintenance manuals (IOMs)Spare partsService locationsResourcesLiteratureCertificatesToolsCompanyAt a glanceOur heritageCommitment to qualityGlobal operationsCareersInvestor relationsSocial responsibilityCorporate identityNewsNews archiveEventsContactSalesServiceInternational operationsMy VelanJoin My VelanForgot your password?
HomePrivacy policy
Email documents
Email these documents
Privacy policyVelan Inc. and its affiliates (“Velan”) are committed to the proper management of the personal information of all visitors to our website (the “site”). This privacy policy (the “policy”) describes how we collect, use, disclose, retain and protect personal information.
What is personal information?
It means any information about an identifiable individual (the “information”). Generally, it does not include information on a business card or available in public records, nor does it include corporate information such as your business address or telephone number in your capacity as an employee of an organization.
Collection of personal information
We limit the amount and the type of information we collect and use to that necessary to fulfill several general purposes or as otherwise permitted or required by law:
to fulfill your requests for services and products
to keep you informed and communicate with you about our products and services
to personalize your experience on our site
to administer our records
to fulfill our legal and professional obligations
Your consent
By providing us with your Information, you consent to its collection, use, and disclosure.
Internet server provider
Certain other information may be collected on the site through various technologies without your actively providing the information. Our site is hosted on servers shared with an Internet service provider (ISP). Any Information collected on our behalf by the ISP is managed in accordance with this policy and is protected by applicable law. Certain information about Internet users’ traffic patterns is passively and automatically collected and linked to users’ Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses. These unique IP addresses are assigned to all Web users by their ISPs, and are automatically logged by Internet servers. While the IP address itself does not identify an individual, it may be used with the cooperation of the ISP to locate and identify an individual using the website.
Server logs
In the normal course of establishing and maintaining Internet connections, our servers automatically log information about visits to our site. Server logs record statistical information. These statistics are reported in aggregate form to us and are used to improve our site and ensure that it provides the optimal online experience for visitors.
Cookies
Like many other websites, our site makes use of “per session” cookie technology. Per session cookies are small text files that contain a unique identification number that is automatically deposited on a visitor’s computer. These cookies track information during an open session and are stored only temporarily in your computer’s memory. This information helps us determine the total number of visitors to the site on an ongoing basis and the types of Internet browsers (e.g., Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) and operating systems (e.g., Windows or Macintosh) that our visitors use. We use this information to facilitate and enhance your online visits. We do not cross-reference this information with any type of Information that is voluntarily offered through the site.
The use of cookie technology is common on the Internet, and many Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies automatically. If you would prefer not to accept cookies, you can set your Internet browser to notify you when your computer is receiving a cookie or to refuse cookies automatically. To readjust your Internet browser’s cookie options, please refer to the instruction documentation of your particular browser or seek online assistance.
Use of personal information
We use information only as described in this policy or as otherwise permitted or required by law. If we distribute publications to people on our mailing lists, you can change your preferences or unsubscribe from our mailing lists.
Disclosure of personal information
We disclose information only as described in this policy or as otherwise permitted or required by law. To provide products or services, we may sometimes disclose our clients’ Information to Velan affiliates and to third parties (for example, to evaluate creditworthiness or to collect debts or to engage experts or consultants), including foreign agents and government or regulatory agencies, or where such disclosure is required or permitted by law.
Our offices around the world may share your Information for marketing purposes.
Your information may be accessed or stored in Canada or another jurisdiction, and will be subject to the laws of that jurisdiction.
Retention of personal information
We will retain information for as long as it is needed for the purposes for which it was collected.
Protection of personal information
We use the standard safeguards to protect the security of Information in our possession, including physical, organizational, and technological measures. We cannot guarantee that information will not be lost, used unlawfully or modified in a fraudulent manner, and consequently we bear no liability for the use that may be made of the information.
Your access to your personal information
You can ask to view your Information by writing to the address provided at the end of this policy. You can request that corrections be made when you can show that the Information we possess is inaccurate.
Links to other websites
The site may contain links to other websites. While we try to link only to websites that share our standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites.
Changes to this policy
We may amend this policy at any time. We will post the policy as amended on our site.
More information
Please contact Velan by phone at (514) 748-7743, or by mail at:
Velan Inc.
ATTN: Legal Department
7007 Cote de Liesse
Montreal, QC  H4T 1G2
CANADA
Velan is a world leader in the design and production of a wide range of cast and forged steel gate, globe, check, ball, triple-offset butterfly, knife gate, highly engineered severe service valves, and steam traps offering superior performance across all major industrial applications.
Products
Cryogenic valvesCast steel Cryogenic valvesAPI 602 small forged cryogenic valvesTorqseal cryogenic triple-offset valvesMemoryseal ball valvesCryogenic control valves
Products (Continued)
Gate, globe, and check valvesPressure seal (forged and cast steel) valvesBolted bonnet high pressure valves (large forged) valvesCast steel (bolted bonnet) valvesCast stainless steel corrosion resistant valvesAPI 602 small forged valvesBonnetless valvesDual-plate check valves (Proquip)Knife gate valvesRAMA easy maintenance valves for nuclear service
HF Acid valvesCast HF acid valvesAPI 602 small forged HF acid valves
Quarter-turn valvesMemoryseal ball valvesSecuraseal metal-seated ball valvesHP series forged ball valvesPower Ball valvesVTP-2000 high performance three-piece ball valvesValvac general purpose ball valvesTorqseal® triple offset valvesVelflex high performance cryogenic butterfly valvesCoker ball valvesCap-Tight batch digester capping valves
Steam trapsBimetallic steam trapsThermodynamic steam traps
Bellows seal valvesBellows seal bolted bonnet high pressure valves (large forged)Bellows seal cast steel valves (Bolted Bonnet)Bellows seal API 602 small forged valves
Velan ABV Valves
Industries servedNuclear powerPowerOil & gasRefiningChemicalPulp & paperMarineMiningLNG & cryogenicsWater & wastewater
ServiceResearch and DevelopmentMaintenance manuals (IOMs)Spare partsService locations
ResourcesLiteratureCertificatesTools
CompanyAt a glanceOur heritageCommitment to qualityGlobal operationsCareersInvestor relationsSocial responsibilityCorporate identityNewsNews archiveEvents
ContactSalesServiceInternational operations
My VelanJoin My VelanForgot your password?Manage my account
© Velan Inc. All rights reserved.
|
Privacy policy |
Terms of use
© Velan Inc. All rights reserved.
Privacy policy |
Terms of use
